1
00:01:39 --> 00:01:41,04
(deep rumbling)

2
00:02:04,08 --> 00:02:07,12 X1:40 X2:600 Y1:20 Y2:50
MAN:
How did we end up here?

3
00:02:12.16 --> 00:02:15.20
This place is horrible.

4
00:02:20.24 --> 00:02:22.28
Smells like balls.

5
00:02:28,32 --> 00:02:31,36
We don't belong
in this shithole.

6
00:02:31,40 --> 00:02:33,44
(computer playing
electronic melody)
